(Sheldon:)so if anyone needs
medical attention
(Sheldon:)or to tell a stranger their
political views are stupid,
(Sheldon:)now's the time.
(Amy:)Have you ever been
off the grid before?
(Howard:)Once.
(Sheldon:)The battery ran out on my phone.
(Sheldon:)I had to wait
for my iPad to turn on.
(Leonard:)I was afraid
he was gonna eat me.
(Howard:)Raj just pulled up.
(Howard:)I'm gonna say something to him.
(Bernadette:)Leave it alone.
He means well.
(Howard:)So you don't think he needs
to rein it in a little?
(Bernadette:)No, not really.
(Howard:)And you're not concerned
(Howard:)he's acting like somehow
this is his kid, too?
(Bernadette:)He's just trying
to be supportive.
(Howard:)Just supportive.
(Howard:)Not over-the-top in any way?
(Penny:)No.
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Hello!
(Bernadette:)You saw him carrying that.
(Howard:)Astronauts saw him
carrying that.